indiahomes.com 2014-12-22

# IndiaHomes

This policy elaborates the procedure of information collected by us and how we uphold your privacy and safeguard all the information provided by you, while providing you our services.

  * ″Website″ means our website accessible at www.indiahomes.com
  * ″Phone Call″ means phone call conversations between you and our Call center agents and property advisors
  * ″Policy″ means this privacy policy as amended from time to time

This Policy applies to the collection, use, processing and access of all information that we collect on the Website. This includes but is not limited to information you upload, conversation you have with us over Phone Calls, emails that you exchange with us and any information submitted by you to us.

The Policy does not apply to, nor do we take any responsibility for, any information that is collected by any third party either using the Website or through any links on the Website or through any of the advertisements. 

Personal/Sensitive/Other information: Defined 

″Personal Information″ implies personally identifiable information like your name, your address, your age, your email address and your phone number 

″Sensitive Personal Information″ which means your financial information, your passwords, any biometric or medical or health related information, or such other information as identified as sensitive personal data or information under the relevant applicable laws in effect. 

″Other Information″ means all other information other than Personal Information, Sensitive Personal Information. To give examples of this, this could be in the nature of device information, your usage patterns, and information you share with us on the type of property you are searching to buy or rent. This includes your preference of city, locality, budget, property type and any other specific need you share on the website or on a Phone call with us or our associates. 

This Policy is effective and applicable to you from the time you register with the Website. For the purposes of this privacy policy, ″you″, ″your″ or ″yourself″ shall mean any person (including a legal entity recognized as a person under law) who is a user of the Website. 

You may also provide information to be published or displayed or posted on the Website, or transmitted to other users of the Website or third parties. Any such information is posted or transmitted to others at your own risk. Please be aware that we cannot control the actions of other users of the Website with whom you may choose to share information with. 

You agree that your personal information provided on the Website may be used to contact you to understand your Property Requirement and to seek your feedback in order to improve the performance of the Website or for advertisements, product offerings, and communications relevant to your use of the Website, and/or to supplement your search of information and material provided on the Website. 

You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of the user name and password assigned to you by the website. However, certain information provided by you to the Website may be saved in the form of cookies while you have the option to change the settings of your internet browsers to prevent such information from being saved. 

#### Security of Personal Information

We take the security of personal information very seriously and have undertaken security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data for the same. The information and data that we receive through the Website is stored on our database, which is stored on servers secured behind a firewall; access to the servers is password-protected and is strictly limited. 

When you use the Website, the services, applications or facilities offered therein, the personal information you share may be visible to other users and can be read, collected, or used by them. You are responsible for the personal information or the sensitive personal data or information you choose to submit in these instances. 

#### Use of your Information:

Our business purposes may include the viewing or advertising of residential or commercial real estate rental/sellable properties or to use of associated services; analytical purposes; data usage; improving the Website or your user experience; providing targeted advertisements to you. 

We share the information on your property requirement with our associates if we in good faith, believe it is required to provide you the service of finding the best property options. We share your personal information like phone number and email with our associates only when we believe that they can offer suitable service to you and should connect with you. 

From time to time, we may use your personal information to send important notices, such as communications about new property listings that may be of interest to you and changes to our terms, conditions, and policies. Whilst this information is important to your interaction with IndiaHomes, you may opt out of receiving these communications by contacting us at support@indiahomes.com or by using corresponding features on our website. 

#### Permitted Disclosures

Besides the above, by law, or by any court or governmental agency or authority for IndiaHomes to disclose your sensitive personal data or information. We may also disclose your sensitive personal data or information if we determine that for purposes of national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance, such disclosure is necessary or appropriate. We may also disclose information about you if we determine that disclosure is reasonably necessary to enforce our terms and conditions or protect our operations or users. Additionally, in the event of a reorganization, merger, or sale we may transfer any and all personal information we collect to the relevant third party. For the aforesaid purposes, we do not require you prior consent to disclose your personal information. 

#### Third Party Disclosure

By accepting our terms of use, we have been authorized by you to disclose your personal information to third parties who may contact you in order to provide advertisements about properties, goods and services of interest to you. Whilst we enter into legally enforceable contracts with third parties to ensure that there may be no misuse of the personal information they obtain from the Website, we offer or provide no indemnity or guarantee for the same on their behalf. You undertake to not hold us liable for any breach done by any third party of their legally enforceable contracts or arrangements with us, as a result of which you may have suffered or incurred a wrongful loss, or any other person has incurred a wrongful gain. 

Any complaints or concerns with regards to the contents of the Website or of any abuse of law may be raised to our team at support@indiahomes.com 

#### Amendments to the Privacy Policy

To keep up with the ever changing times, we may make changes to the Policy. We will indicate that the Policy has changed and this will be displayed prominently on the Website. You will need to ascertain for yourself what changes have been made or whether or not you agree with the changes. If you do not agree to the changes, you should discontinue your use of the Website, because as we have told your earlier, your use or access of the Website will constitute your acceptance of the Policy as then changed. 

#### Terms of Use:

This Privacy policy shall be read with and form a part of the Terms of Use.

#### Grievance Redressal

If you have any complaints about the Website, its contents or anything in relation thereto, please contact our grievance redressal team at support@indiahomes.com
